{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5103","name":"Detroit Water Ice Factory ","address":"1014 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226","owner":"DWIF LLC.","licenseNumber":"200079","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.04668,42.33280","geojson":{"id":"5103","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.046682203,42.332796403]},"properties":{"name":"Detroit Water Ice Factory ","owner":"DWIF LLC.","address":"1014 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"200079","establishmentid":"5103","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"4/29/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5327","name":"Detroit Water Ice Factory","address":"1014 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5226","name":"Calexico","address":"1040 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4321","name":"Texas De Brazil","address":"1000 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2728","name":"Hard Rock Cafe","address":"45 Monroe St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5325","name":"Tim Hortons","address":"49 Monroe St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2709","name":"Eurest Dining Services-Compuware","address":"1 Campus Martius","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4954","name":"Freshii ","address":"1001 Woodward","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4265","name":"Slices Pizza","address":"1043 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5364","name":"Avalon Hearth and Soul Cafe","address":"1049 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5392","name":"800 Parc","address":"800 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"52031","inspectionDate":"2020-07-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-07-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-07-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"49870","inspectionDate":"2019-11-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"front","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-11-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"8-304.11","violationDescription":"Upon acceptance of the PERMIT issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, the PERMIT HOLDER in order to retain the PERMIT shall:\r\n(A) Post the PERMIT in a location in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT that is conspicuous to CONSUMERS; \r\n(B) Comply with the provisions of this Code including the conditions of a granted VARIANCE as specified under § 8-103.12, and APPROVED plans as specified under § 8-201.12;\r\n(C) If a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT is required under § 8-201.13 to operate under a HACCP PLAN, comply with the plan as specified under § 8-103.12;\r\n(D) Immediately contact the REGULATORY AUTHORITY to report an illness of a FOOD EMPLOYEE or CONDITIONAL EMPLOYEE as specified under ¶ 2-201.11(B); \r\n(E) Immediately discontinue operations and notify the REGULATORY AUTHORITY if an IMMINENT HEALTH HAZARD may exist as specified under § 8-404.11;\r\n(F) Allow representatives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY access to the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT as specified under § 8-402.11;\r\n(G) Except as specified under ¶ (H) of this section, replace existing facilities and EQUIPMENT specified in § 8-101.10 with facilities and EQUIPMENT that comply with this Code if:\r\n(1) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement because the facilities and EQUIPMENT constitute a public health HAZARD or nuisance or no longer comply with the criteria upon which the facilities and EQUIPMENT were accepted,\r\n(2) The REGULATORY AUTHORITY directs the replacement of the facilities and EQUIPMENT because of a change of ownership, or\r\n(3) The facilities and EQUIPMENT are replaced in the normal course of operation;\r\n(H) Upgrade or replace refrigeration EQUIPMENT as specified under Subparagraph 3-501.16(A)(2)(b), if the circumstances specified under Subparagraphs (G)(1) - (3) of this section do not occur first, and 5 years pass after the REGULATORY AUTHORITY adopts this Code;\r\n(I) Comply with directives of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY in regard to the PERMIT HOLDER'S FOOD ESTABLISHMENT or in response to community emergencies; \r\n(J) Accept notices issued and served by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY according to LAW; and \r\n(K) Be subject to the administrative, civil, injunctive, and criminal remedies authorized in LAW for failure to comply with this Code or a directive of the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, including time frames for corrective actions specified in inspection reports, notices, orders, warnings, and other directives.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.12","violationDescription":"FOOD may not be stored:\r\n(A)  In locker rooms;\r\n(B)  In toilet rooms;\r\n(C)  In dressing rooms;\r\n(D)  In garbage rooms;\r\n(E)  In mechanical rooms;\r\n(F)  Under sewer lines that are not shielded to intercept potential drips;\r\n(G)  Under leaking water lines, including leaking automatic fire sprinkler heads, or        under lines on which water has condensed;\r\n(H)  Under open stairwells; or\r\n(I)   Under other sources of contamination.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food(s) stored","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In prohibited area(s)","subProblem":"In or under other sources of contamination","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-11-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate to a suitable storage area"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-11-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"48075","inspectionDate":"2019-06-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-06-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44870","inspectionDate":"2019-01-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"Under the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Cleaned when food items are exposed","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean in sanitary manner when no food items are exposed."}]},{"inspectionid":"42843","inspectionDate":"2018-07-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"40052","inspectionDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"NON-FOOD CONTACT SURFACES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"38073","inspectionDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the Past date food","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"back","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36391","inspectionDate":"2016-09-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-203.14","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be installed to preclude backflow of contaminants into the water supply system at each point of use at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT by providing an air gap or installing an APPROVED backflow prevention device. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow prevention","subItem":"backflow/backsiphonage device","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COFFEE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide additional equipment to meet requirement above."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Raw ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-09-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5103"}}